<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<search>
    <total_items>1179</total_items>
    <page_size>10</page_size>
    <page_count>118</page_count>
    <page_number>1</page_number>
    <page_items></page_items>
    <first_item></first_item>
    <last_item></last_item>
    <search_time>0.101</search_time>
    <events>
        <event id="E0-001-123078006-2">
            <title>YOGA MUSIC CHANTS AND SONGS - HEALING AND GROWTH THROUGH MUSIC</title>
            <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/yoga-music-chants-and-songs-healing-and-growth-t-/E0-001-123078006-2?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
            <description> Well-Being and Healing Through Singing We sing because itâ??s empowering, we sing because itâ??s healing, we sing because itâ??s relaxing, we sing because it cleanses, we sing to boost our immune systems, we sing because it brings us closer, we sing for our world and our planet, we sing because itâ??s fun, we sing to love deeper and we sing because it connects us to source. In these magical interactive sessions Lorrayn will lead Chants inspired by her Kundalini Yoga practice and some of the beautiful, simple, easy to learn Folk and Gospel songs from her teaching practice. I invite you to come and sing the beautiful Chants and Spiritual Songs I have gathered after 30 years of leading voice/singing/choir groups/workshops/classes of all kinds. Many of the chants are taken from my Kundalini Yoga practise, others are from other chanting traditions I have practised, some I have written myself and we also sing some Gospel songs.Â  Â  Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â  The Aim Is Always the Same â?? To Connect to SOURCE Â If you are a singer, then you are welcome to join in and if not then you are very welcome to come and just listen to the music we will be creating. There is no compulsion to join in. Many people come just to experience the spiritual vibration of the chants and feel the comradery of being with like-minded people. Every person present contributes their own unique energy to the gathering even if you donâ??t sing. However, the more singers the better. I will teach you the chants and songs. It would be true to say that all the songs have a strong spiritual component. The Vibration of The Sound -The Inspiration of The Melody and The Lyric Having a regular spiritual practice of our own (even if it is unstructured to start with like regular walks in nature, painting or yoga etc) and chanting especially can help create a powerful aura around us and stop another peopleâ??s negativity sticking to us. It is something that needs to be PRACTISED on a regular basis. In the same way that we practice eating well and exercising to maintain physical fitness, spiritual fitness also needs to be practiced.Â Chanting is a spiritual practise and my aim is for us to transmit that healing energy to ourselves, to each other and out into the world through the music. Â  Lorrayn de Peyer is a professional singer with twenty-five yearsâ?? experience leading singing groups, workshops and choirs; and over thirty years of practicing yoga and meditation. She is the founder and Director of THE COURAGE TO SING a national school of voice and singing. Â  Sacred singing can also be used for sacred occasions to uplift people at events of heightened emotion like births, deaths, times of grief or suffering as well as times of special celebrations. Perhaps some of you know occasions where we can go and sing to ease peoples pain or add to their celebration. Â Privacy: Please note that in alignment with the latest GDPR compliancy laws in the UK we wish to notify you that by registering for this workshop you are giving Lorrayn de Peyer and her team permission to contact you by email regarding details about this workshop, news and events put on by COURAGE ENTERPRISES. You have the option to unsubscribe at any time and your email address will under not circumstances be shared with any third party. We thank you for your consideration and support of our wish to uphold and guard your privacy at all times. FAQs Â·Â Â Â Â  Who is this event aimed at? All singers of all levels and people who enjoy listening/joining in to chanting, singing spiritual gospel and folk songs. Â·Â Â Â Â  What will I get out of this event? This is a powerful and interactive workshop aimed to give you the experience of transformation on a psychological and energetic level from the music. Event details? Where: The Marylebone Studios, 29 Marylebone Lane, Marylebone, London W1U 2NQ (a convenient venue right in the middle of Londonâ??s most elite shopping area) Â·Â Â Â Â  Who is the organizer of the event? Lorrayn de Peyer for COURAGE enterprises Â·Â Â Â Â  Who to contact with any questions? Please email welcome@lorrayndepeyer.com Â·Â Â Â Â  What is the refund policy? 7 DAYS -Â  please let us know as soon as possible Â·Â Â Â Â  Is it OK if the name on the registration/ticket doesn&amp;#39;t match the person attending Is that okay? Yes, but please let us know the correct name of the attendee prior to the event. Â·Â Â Â Â  What can/can&amp;#39;t I bring into the event? The event has a behind closed doors policy, so you may not bring recording devices. Bring some water to drink. Can you give in-house training upon request for my team / business? Yes, we have a wide range of team building and coaching sessions available. Please go to http://www.lorrayndepeyer.com/team-building-activities/ Â·Â Â Â Â  Do you give 1-2-1 Coaching Sessions? Yes. Please contact our office via email welcome@lorrayndepeyer.com or by mobile at 07779946444. You can find out more about coaching and training on our web site â?? http://www.lorrayndepeyer.com/inspirational-life-coaching-manifesting-miracles Â  Testimonials from COURAGE workshop participants â??Brilliant, really really enjoyed it, everybody got into it, â??Ten out of Tenâ?? Allestons Solicitors â??Wonderful. Wonderful. Wonderful. Thank you soooo much for pushing me in the right direction and making me feel very heldâ?? Annabel, London â??I have held myself back career wise because I have avoided any kind of limelight position in big meetings and by not doing presentationsâ?¦But not anymore!â?? Jules, Exeter, Devon â??You have put into place a method that is based upon gentle nurturing, but at the same time does not shy away from the fact that at some point fears have to be faced, but only after the groundwork, the confidence building has taken place - your method works, and this has not come about by chance it has come about by meticulous planning on your part.â?? Jack, Weekend Workshop â??A wonderful introduction â??Thank youâ?? Rory, London â??I have more energy and I have become more effective as a human beingâ?? Maria, London, Life Coach â??Wow â?? what an experience. Thanks for all your wisdom, warmth and supportâ?? Emma, London â??Just want to say thank you so very muchâ?¦I have learnt a lot and would never have had the confidence to do anything like this without youâ?? Sheila, Dorset â??Amazingâ?¦a really uplifting experienceâ?? Christine M â??Really practical information and very inspiring. I feel ready to do this nowâ?? Karen London Â  Â  </description>
            <start_time>2019-03-15 14:30:00</start_time>
            <stop_time></stop_time>
            <tz_id></tz_id>
            <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
            <tz_country></tz_country>
            <tz_city></tz_city>
            <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
            <venue_id>V0-001-012927618-7</venue_id>
            <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/the-music-studios-/V0-001-012927618-7?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
            <venue_name>The Music Studios</venue_name>
            <venue_display>1</venue_display>
            <venue_address>29 Marylebone Lane</venue_address>
            <city_name>London</city_name>
            <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
            <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
            <postal_code></postal_code>
            <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
            <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
            <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
            <latitude>51.5166917</latitude>
            <longitude>-0.1506739</longitude>
            <geocode_type>EVDB Geocoder</geocode_type>
            <all_day>0</all_day>
            <recur_string></recur_string>
            <calendar_count></calendar_count>
            <comment_count></comment_count>
            <link_count></link_count>
            <going_count></going_count>
            <watching_count></watching_count>
            <created>2019-02-04 02:24:36</created>
            <owner>evdb</owner>
            <modified>2019-02-04 17:10:04</modified>
            <performers></performers>
            <image></image>
            <privacy>1</privacy>
            <calendars></calendars>
            <groups></groups>
            <going></going>
        </event>
        <event id="E0-001-117477206-0@2019042616">
            <title>Undercover Festival VII (2019)</title>
            <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/undercover-festival-vii-20-/E0-001-117477206-0@2019042616?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
            <description>UNDERCOVER FESTIVAL VII a 3 day celebration of alternative music including Punk / Post Punk + much more. On the move to London Boston Music Room / The Dome Tufnell Park London (very near Tufnell Park Tube Station).  26, 27 &amp; 28 April 2019 It is once again held undercover i.e. not outdoors so if itâ??s peeing down come April itâ??s not a problem and your beer wonâ??t get diluted. Leave your wellies at home, and enjoy one of the best small alternative festivals London and the South East has to offer in APRIL 2019.Undercover Festival boasts main acts such as Sham 69 (Pursey, Parsons, Treganna, Guy) / Slaughter and the Dogs / Penetration / GBH plus a very strong supporting line up of bands that to any lover of alternative music will find more than appealing.All bands have been announced see WWW.UNDERCOVERFEST.COM for details</description>
            <start_time>2019-04-26 16:00:00</start_time>
            <stop_time>2019-04-27 02:00:00</stop_time>
            <tz_id></tz_id>
            <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
            <tz_country></tz_country>
            <tz_city></tz_city>
            <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
            <venue_id>V0-001-012058105-9</venue_id>
            <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/boston-music-room-/V0-001-012058105-9?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
            <venue_name>Boston Music Room</venue_name>
            <venue_display>1</venue_display>
            <venue_address>178 Junction Road, London, LND N19 5QQ</venue_address>
            <city_name>London</city_name>
            <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
            <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
            <postal_code></postal_code>
            <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
            <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
            <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
            <latitude>51.557269</latitude>
            <longitude>-0.138371</longitude>
            <geocode_type>EVDB Geocoder</geocode_type>
            <all_day>0</all_day>
            <recur_string>every 3 days for 1 times</recur_string>
            <calendar_count></calendar_count>
            <comment_count></comment_count>
            <link_count></link_count>
            <going_count></going_count>
            <watching_count></watching_count>
            <created>2018-08-27 04:26:32</created>
            <owner>UndercoverFestival</owner>
            <modified>2018-08-27 04:26:32</modified>
            <performers></performers>
            <image>
                <url>http://d1marr3m5x4iac.cloudfront.net/images/small/I0-001/041/015/988-9.png_/undercover-festival-vii-2019-88.png</url>
                <width>48</width>
                <height>48</height>
                <caption></caption>
                <thumb>
                    <url>http://d1marr3m5x4iac.cloudfront.net/images/thumb/I0-001/041/015/988-9.png_/undercover-festival-vii-2019-88.png</url>
                    <width>48</width>
                    <height>48</height>
                </thumb>
                <small>
                    <url>http://d1marr3m5x4iac.cloudfront.net/images/small/I0-001/041/015/988-9.png_/undercover-festival-vii-2019-88.png</url>
                    <width>48</width>
                    <height>48</height>
                </small>
                <medium>
                    <url>http://d1marr3m5x4iac.cloudfront.net/images/medium/I0-001/041/015/988-9.png_/undercover-festival-vii-2019-88.png</url>
                    <width>128</width>
                    <height>128</height>
                </medium>
            </image>
            <privacy>1</privacy>
            <calendars></calendars>
            <groups></groups>
            <going></going>
        </event>
        <event id="E0-001-117769776-0">
            <title>To The Rats And Wolves London</title>
            <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/rats-and-wolves-london-/E0-001-117769776-0?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
            <description> Buy those To The Rats And Wolves London tickets before they all run out! This is your chance to experience a one-of-a-kind show, as To The Rats And Wolves will be live on stage at Boston Music Room. Take this chance to listen to the best songs of To The Rats And Wolves live and buy your To The Rats And Wolves LondonÂ ticketsÂ at StubHub.</description>
            <start_time>2019-03-22 19:00:00</start_time>
            <stop_time></stop_time>
            <tz_id></tz_id>
            <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
            <tz_country></tz_country>
            <tz_city></tz_city>
            <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
            <venue_id>V0-001-012058105-9</venue_id>
            <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/boston-music-room-/V0-001-012058105-9?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
            <venue_name>Boston Music Room</venue_name>
            <venue_display>1</venue_display>
            <venue_address>178 Junction Road, London, LND N19 5QQ</venue_address>
            <city_name>London</city_name>
            <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
            <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
            <postal_code></postal_code>
            <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
            <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
            <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
            <latitude>51.557269</latitude>
            <longitude>-0.138371</longitude>
            <geocode_type>EVDB Geocoder</geocode_type>
            <all_day>0</all_day>
            <recur_string></recur_string>
            <calendar_count></calendar_count>
            <comment_count></comment_count>
            <link_count></link_count>
            <going_count></going_count>
            <watching_count></watching_count>
            <created>2018-09-06 05:28:24</created>
            <owner>evdb</owner>
            <modified>2018-09-06 05:28:24</modified>
            <performers></performers>
            <image></image>
            <privacy>1</privacy>
            <calendars></calendars>
            <groups></groups>
            <going></going>
        </event>
        <event id="E0-001-122546242-7">
            <title>Portals Presents: Her Name is Calla - Final UK Show</title>
            <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/portals-presents-her-name-calla-final-uk-show-/E0-001-122546242-7?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
            <description> After almost 15 years, British post-rock heroes Her Name Is Calla are calling it a day. Portals are proud to present their final UK show, at the Boston Music Room, on Saturday 4th May, with support from Katie Malco. The band have brought elements of folk storytelling and classical instrumentation to an otherwise codified genre and have always been hard to place. Nevertheless, their captivating records and live sets have drawn praise from all quarters of the music press: the NME described them as &amp;quot;massive, pastorally apocalyptic music&amp;quot;, whilst Drowned in Sound called them &amp;quot;one of the most daring, unconventional bands the UK has to offer&amp;quot;, and their album &amp;#39;The Quiet Lamb&amp;#39; currently ranks as the 16th best post-rock album of all-time according to a fans poll. Safe to say they will be sorely missed. The band will play an extended set in an intimate venue so as to play songs from all their albums. A special evening beckons. </description>
            <start_time>2019-05-04 19:00:00</start_time>
            <stop_time></stop_time>
            <tz_id></tz_id>
            <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
            <tz_country></tz_country>
            <tz_city></tz_city>
            <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
            <venue_id>V0-001-005495431-4</venue_id>
            <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/boston-arms-music-room-/V0-001-005495431-4?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
            <venue_name>Boston Arms Music Room</venue_name>
            <venue_display>1</venue_display>
            <venue_address>178 Junction Road</venue_address>
            <city_name>London</city_name>
            <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
            <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
            <postal_code></postal_code>
            <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
            <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
            <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
            <latitude>51.557269</latitude>
            <longitude>-0.138371</longitude>
            <geocode_type>EVDB Geocoder</geocode_type>
            <all_day>0</all_day>
            <recur_string></recur_string>
            <calendar_count></calendar_count>
            <comment_count></comment_count>
            <link_count></link_count>
            <going_count></going_count>
            <watching_count></watching_count>
            <created>2019-01-22 08:26:55</created>
            <owner>evdb</owner>
            <modified>2019-01-22 08:26:55</modified>
            <performers>
                <performer>
                    <id>P0-001-000275052-4</id>
                    <url>http://concerts.eventful.com/Her-Name-is-Calla?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
                    <name>Her Name is Calla</name>
                    <short_bio>Alternative</short_bio>
                    <creator>evdb</creator>
                    <linker>evdb</linker>
                </performer>
            </performers>
            <image>
                <url>http://d1marr3m5x4iac.cloudfront.net/images/small/I0-001/004/351/536-8.jpeg_/her-name-is-calla-36.jpeg</url>
                <width>48</width>
                <height>48</height>
                <caption></caption>
                <thumb>
                    <url>http://d1marr3m5x4iac.cloudfront.net/images/thumb/I0-001/004/351/536-8.jpeg_/her-name-is-calla-36.jpeg</url>
                    <width>48</width>
                    <height>48</height>
                </thumb>
                <small>
                    <url>http://d1marr3m5x4iac.cloudfront.net/images/small/I0-001/004/351/536-8.jpeg_/her-name-is-calla-36.jpeg</url>
                    <width>48</width>
                    <height>48</height>
                </small>
                <medium>
                    <url>http://d1marr3m5x4iac.cloudfront.net/images/medium/I0-001/004/351/536-8.jpeg_/her-name-is-calla-36.jpeg</url>
                    <width>128</width>
                    <height>128</height>
                </medium>
            </image>
            <privacy>1</privacy>
            <calendars></calendars>
            <groups></groups>
            <going></going>
        </event>
        <event id="E0-001-121150786-6">
            <title>Bishop Gunn London</title>
            <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/bishop-gunn-london-/E0-001-121150786-6?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
            <description> The day that you have been expecting for months is finally here! Bishop Gunn will be taking the stage atÂ Boston Music Room in a few days and tickets are selling out very fast! After so long, you can&amp;#39;t miss out on seeing your favourite artists perform live. Therefore, buy your Bishop Gunn London tickets as soon as possible and attend this incredible event! Get ready to jump, to sing and to dance and especially to feel the excitement during the whole concert! You will, without a doubt, have the best time ever. Don&amp;#39;t hesitate! Purchase yourÂ Bishop Gunn London tickets and have the time of your life!</description>
            <start_time>2019-02-27 19:00:00</start_time>
            <stop_time></stop_time>
            <tz_id></tz_id>
            <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
            <tz_country></tz_country>
            <tz_city></tz_city>
            <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
            <venue_id>V0-001-012058105-9</venue_id>
            <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/boston-music-room-/V0-001-012058105-9?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
            <venue_name>Boston Music Room</venue_name>
            <venue_display>1</venue_display>
            <venue_address>178 Junction Road, London, LND N19 5QQ</venue_address>
            <city_name>London</city_name>
            <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
            <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
            <postal_code></postal_code>
            <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
            <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
            <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
            <latitude>51.557269</latitude>
            <longitude>-0.138371</longitude>
            <geocode_type>EVDB Geocoder</geocode_type>
            <all_day>0</all_day>
            <recur_string></recur_string>
            <calendar_count></calendar_count>
            <comment_count></comment_count>
            <link_count></link_count>
            <going_count></going_count>
            <watching_count></watching_count>
            <created>2018-12-13 06:24:59</created>
            <owner>evdb</owner>
            <modified>2018-12-13 06:24:59</modified>
            <performers></performers>
            <image></image>
            <privacy>1</privacy>
            <calendars></calendars>
            <groups></groups>
            <going></going>
        </event>
        <event id="E0-001-122510885-7">
            <title>Lloyd Life Presents '30 Life'</title>
            <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/lloyd-life-presents-30-life-/E0-001-122510885-7?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
            <description> LloydÂ Life would like his loyal friends and family who have supported him and his events over the past 30 years to join him at Westbank Gallery on Saturday 16th February 2019 for 30 Life!Â If you have ever attended any of his events over the years, you will know his house is your house!Â This will be the first in a series of 30 life events this year to celebrate a milestone within this ever-evolving music industry.Â Â  See you all on the dance floor! </description>
            <start_time>2019-02-16 22:00:00</start_time>
            <stop_time></stop_time>
            <tz_id></tz_id>
            <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
            <tz_country></tz_country>
            <tz_city></tz_city>
            <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
            <venue_id>V0-001-011297308-8</venue_id>
            <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/westbank-art-music-/V0-001-011297308-8?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
            <venue_name>Westbank Art &amp; Music</venue_name>
            <venue_display>1</venue_display>
            <venue_address>3-5 Thorpe Close</venue_address>
            <city_name>London</city_name>
            <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
            <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
            <postal_code></postal_code>
            <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
            <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
            <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
            <latitude>51.5180465</latitude>
            <longitude>-0.2093711</longitude>
            <geocode_type>EVDB Geocoder</geocode_type>
            <all_day>0</all_day>
            <recur_string></recur_string>
            <calendar_count></calendar_count>
            <comment_count></comment_count>
            <link_count></link_count>
            <going_count></going_count>
            <watching_count></watching_count>
            <created>2019-01-20 11:58:37</created>
            <owner>evdb</owner>
            <modified>2019-01-20 11:58:37</modified>
            <performers></performers>
            <image>
                <url>http://d1marr3m5x4iac.cloudfront.net/images/small/I0-001/042/439/245-4.jpeg_/lloyd-life-presents-30-life-45.jpeg</url>
                <width>48</width>
                <height>48</height>
                <caption></caption>
                <thumb>
                    <url>http://d1marr3m5x4iac.cloudfront.net/images/thumb/I0-001/042/439/245-4.jpeg_/lloyd-life-presents-30-life-45.jpeg</url>
                    <width>48</width>
                    <height>48</height>
                </thumb>
                <small>
                    <url>http://d1marr3m5x4iac.cloudfront.net/images/small/I0-001/042/439/245-4.jpeg_/lloyd-life-presents-30-life-45.jpeg</url>
                    <width>48</width>
                    <height>48</height>
                </small>
                <medium>
                    <url>http://d1marr3m5x4iac.cloudfront.net/images/medium/I0-001/042/439/245-4.jpeg_/lloyd-life-presents-30-life-45.jpeg</url>
                    <width>128</width>
                    <height>128</height>
                </medium>
            </image>
            <privacy>1</privacy>
            <calendars></calendars>
            <groups></groups>
            <going></going>
        </event>
        <event id="E0-001-119955530-5">
            <title>Lost Society London</title>
            <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/lost-society-london-/E0-001-119955530-5?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
            <description> Get &amp;#39;em while they&amp;#39;re hot! Â Lost Society London tickets are waiting for you here at StubHub, so you&amp;#39;d better pluck some up for yourself while supplies last. Â On our online booking system, you will find a wide range of all types of tickets to concerts worldwide! Â But, for now, set your eye on the prize - the tickets forÂ Lost Society London that will get you intoÂ Boston Music Room to watch the liveÂ Lost Society performance. Â You can be there with just a few simple and secure steps. Â Count on StubHub and purchase yourÂ Lost Society London tickets today!</description>
            <start_time>2019-02-15 19:00:00</start_time>
            <stop_time></stop_time>
            <tz_id></tz_id>
            <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
            <tz_country></tz_country>
            <tz_city></tz_city>
            <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
            <venue_id>V0-001-012058105-9</venue_id>
            <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/boston-music-room-/V0-001-012058105-9?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
            <venue_name>Boston Music Room</venue_name>
            <venue_display>1</venue_display>
            <venue_address>178 Junction Road, London, LND N19 5QQ</venue_address>
            <city_name>London</city_name>
            <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
            <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
            <postal_code></postal_code>
            <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
            <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
            <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
            <latitude>51.557269</latitude>
            <longitude>-0.138371</longitude>
            <geocode_type>EVDB Geocoder</geocode_type>
            <all_day>0</all_day>
            <recur_string></recur_string>
            <calendar_count></calendar_count>
            <comment_count></comment_count>
            <link_count></link_count>
            <going_count></going_count>
            <watching_count></watching_count>
            <created>2018-11-10 05:16:00</created>
            <owner>evdb</owner>
            <modified>2018-11-10 05:16:00</modified>
            <performers></performers>
            <image></image>
            <privacy>1</privacy>
            <calendars></calendars>
            <groups></groups>
            <going></going>
        </event>
        <event id="E0-001-122933644-9">
            <title>Point Blank London Open Day</title>
            <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/point-blank-london-open-day-/E0-001-122933644-9?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
            <description> The Open Day is the perfect opportunity to visit our campus and learn more about our Higher Education music production, sound engineering, DJ and music industry courses. The day will include a tour of our state-of-the-art studio facilities and an exclusive track deconstructionÂ from our Head of Curriculum, Ski Oakenfull. Our Course Advisors and Admissions Staff will be on hand to answer any questions you have. Our Open Days get fully booked well in advance so make sure you register as soon as possible.Â  Please register one ticket per person attending, you will only be able to book a maximum of two tickets per person. Please aim to arrive around 12:45 for a 13:00 start. Refreshments will be available.Â  The Programme 13:00 - 13:15: Introductory SeminarÂ  Course Advisors present an overview of Point Blank and our range of courses. 13:15 - 15:00: Tour, Masterclass and Your Questions AnsweredÂ  Tour of the facilities Exclusive track deconstruction from Head of Curriculum, Ski Oakenfull Chance to speak to our Course Advisors, Student Reps and Expert Instructors If you have any questions about the Open Day, please donâ??t hesitate to contact us. We hope to see you there! </description>
            <start_time>2019-03-02 13:00:00</start_time>
            <stop_time></stop_time>
            <tz_id></tz_id>
            <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
            <tz_country></tz_country>
            <tz_city></tz_city>
            <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
            <venue_id>V0-001-009623147-1</venue_id>
            <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/point-blank-music-school-/V0-001-009623147-1?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
            <venue_name>Point Blank Music School</venue_name>
            <venue_display>1</venue_display>
            <venue_address>26 Orsman Road</venue_address>
            <city_name>London</city_name>
            <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
            <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
            <postal_code></postal_code>
            <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
            <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
            <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
            <latitude>51.5365376</latitude>
            <longitude>-0.0800987</longitude>
            <geocode_type>EVDB Geocoder</geocode_type>
            <all_day>0</all_day>
            <recur_string></recur_string>
            <calendar_count></calendar_count>
            <comment_count></comment_count>
            <link_count></link_count>
            <going_count></going_count>
            <watching_count></watching_count>
            <created>2019-02-01 15:02:31</created>
            <owner>evdb</owner>
            <modified>2019-02-01 15:02:31</modified>
            <performers></performers>
            <image>
                <url>http://d1marr3m5x4iac.cloudfront.net/images/small/I0-001/042/566/575-5.jpeg_/point-blank-london-open-day-75.jpeg</url>
                <width>48</width>
                <height>48</height>
                <caption></caption>
                <thumb>
                    <url>http://d1marr3m5x4iac.cloudfront.net/images/thumb/I0-001/042/566/575-5.jpeg_/point-blank-london-open-day-75.jpeg</url>
                    <width>48</width>
                    <height>48</height>
                </thumb>
                <small>
                    <url>http://d1marr3m5x4iac.cloudfront.net/images/small/I0-001/042/566/575-5.jpeg_/point-blank-london-open-day-75.jpeg</url>
                    <width>48</width>
                    <height>48</height>
                </small>
                <medium>
                    <url>http://d1marr3m5x4iac.cloudfront.net/images/medium/I0-001/042/566/575-5.jpeg_/point-blank-london-open-day-75.jpeg</url>
                    <width>128</width>
                    <height>128</height>
                </medium>
            </image>
            <privacy>1</privacy>
            <calendars></calendars>
            <groups></groups>
            <going></going>
        </event>
        <event id="E0-001-115114717-7@2019021414">
            <title>Aladdin The Musical London</title>
            <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/aladdin-musical-london-/E0-001-115114717-7@2019021414?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
            <description> Aladdin The Musical London is one of the most successful musicals of these days. Aladdin The Musical London at Prince Edward Theatre is popular among all types of audience. Make sure you donÂ´t miss Aladdin The Musical London at Prince Edward Theatre and buy your tickets now before they are completely sold out. You can find the best tickets for Aladdin The Musical London at StubHub.</description>
            <start_time>2019-02-14 14:30:00</start_time>
            <stop_time></stop_time>
            <tz_id></tz_id>
            <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
            <tz_country></tz_country>
            <tz_city></tz_city>
            <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
            <venue_id>V0-001-012057653-4</venue_id>
            <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/prince-edward-theatre-/V0-001-012057653-4?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
            <venue_name>Prince Edward Theatre</venue_name>
            <venue_display>1</venue_display>
            <venue_address>Old Compton Street, London, London W1V6HS</venue_address>
            <city_name>London</city_name>
            <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
            <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
            <postal_code></postal_code>
            <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
            <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
            <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
            <latitude>51.5135117</latitude>
            <longitude>-0.1307417</longitude>
            <geocode_type>EVDB Geocoder</geocode_type>
            <all_day>0</all_day>
            <recur_string>on various days</recur_string>
            <calendar_count></calendar_count>
            <comment_count></comment_count>
            <link_count></link_count>
            <going_count></going_count>
            <watching_count></watching_count>
            <created>2018-06-07 03:07:47</created>
            <owner>evdb</owner>
            <modified>2019-02-09 07:29:52</modified>
            <performers></performers>
            <image></image>
            <privacy>1</privacy>
            <calendars></calendars>
            <groups></groups>
            <going></going>
        </event>
        <event id="E0-001-115079629-5@2019021414">
            <title>Motown the Musical London</title>
            <url>http://london.eventful.com/events/motown-musical-london-/E0-001-115079629-5@2019021414?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</url>
            <description> Motown the Musical London is one of the most successful musicals of these days. Motown the Musical London at Shaftesbury Theatre is popular among all types of audience. Make sure you donÂ´t miss Motown the Musical London at Shaftesbury Theatre and buy your tickets now before they are completely sold out. You can find the best tickets for Motown the Musical London at StubHub.</description>
            <start_time>2019-02-14 14:30:00</start_time>
            <stop_time></stop_time>
            <tz_id></tz_id>
            <tz_olson_path></tz_olson_path>
            <tz_country></tz_country>
            <tz_city></tz_city>
            <olson_path>Europe/London</olson_path>
            <venue_id>V0-001-012057662-2</venue_id>
            <venue_url>http://london.eventful.com/venues/shaftesbury-theatre-/V0-001-012057662-2?utm_source=apis&amp;utm_medium=apim&amp;utm_campaign=apic</venue_url>
            <venue_name>Shaftesbury Theatre</venue_name>
            <venue_display>1</venue_display>
            <venue_address>210 Shaftesbury Avenue, London, London WC2H8DP</venue_address>
            <city_name>London</city_name>
            <region_name>Greater London</region_name>
            <region_abbr>London</region_abbr>
            <postal_code></postal_code>
            <country_name>United Kingdom</country_name>
            <country_abbr2>GB</country_abbr2>
            <country_abbr>GBR</country_abbr>
            <latitude>51.5162133</latitude>
            <longitude>-0.1260628</longitude>
            <geocode_type>EVDB Geocoder</geocode_type>
            <all_day>0</all_day>
            <recur_string>on various days</recur_string>
            <calendar_count></calendar_count>
            <comment_count></comment_count>
            <link_count></link_count>
            <going_count></going_count>
            <watching_count></watching_count>
            <created>2018-06-06 07:44:40</created>
            <owner>evdb</owner>
            <modified>2018-09-21 06:40:33</modified>
            <performers></performers>
            <image></image>
            <privacy>1</privacy>
            <calendars></calendars>
            <groups></groups>
            <going></going>
        </event>
    </events>
</search>